http://www.fitnesswarehouse.com.au/pages/privacy-policy

Fitness Warehouse Privacy Policy
Fitness Warehouse collects customer information to help us to serve you better. We respect your privacy and are committed to maintaining and using this information responsibly. This privacy policy addresses the use and disclosure of personal information we collect from you. By visiting our website, or providing your information to us, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.
Information we collect about you
Any personal information you provide to us is maintained on secure servers and our internal systems. We collect information when you register online or update your account, log-in, place an order, opt-in to receive our emails, shop online, request a catalogue or participate in contests, promotions or surveys. This information may include, but is not limited to, your contact information (for example, your name, email address, billing and shipping addresses and phone number) and your credit card information. If you create an online account, you also have the option of providing your product preferences. If you use our “email this to a friend” functionality found on all product pages, or if you choose to send an email from our site to a friend, we will also collect your friend’s name and email address. Your friend’s information is only used to send the forwarding email and is not saved in our customer or marketing databases. In addition to the information that you voluntarily provide when using our site, we may also record information that your web browser routinely shares with websites. This may include your browser type, browser language, Internet Protocol address, software and hardware attributes, the date and time of your visit, the geographical location of the Internet Protocol address, and the pages that you visit. This will generally be anonymous data that we collect on an aggregate basis. We will not try to associate anonymous data with your personally identifiable data.
How we use this information
When you place an order on the website, we use this information to process and track your order and contact you via email, postal mail or phone if we have any questions or concerns regarding your order. If you provide an email address, you will also receive order confirmation and shipping status emails. We also maintain a record of your purchases made on our website in order to serve you better. We may also use information about your product preferences and interests in order to improve our site design and enhance your shopping experience. When we offer contests, promotions or surveys, you may be required to provide certain personal information so we can notify winners and/or fulfill promotional obligations. In these instances, you have the option to receive emails or other communications from us regarding our products, services, contests, and promotions. Even if you have previously chosen not to receive email or postal mail from us, you may still receive information as it relates to the sweepstakes, contest, promotion or survey in which you have participated. Fitness Warehouse uses third parties who perform tasks on our behalf, such as our web developers, and we require them to follow these same privacy practices. In the unlikely event of a sale of our business, Fitness Warehouse may disclose your personal information to a purchaser that agrees to abide by the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. You should also be aware that we may disclose specific information about you if required to do so by law, governmental request, to respond to subpoenas, court orders, administrative orders or other legal process or based on our good faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with such law, request or court order, to prevent fraud, to protect our rights or to protect the users of our websites or the public.
Changing Address
If you want to change your postal or email address, please send an email to inquiries@fitnesswarehouse.com.au with the following:
The phrase “address change” in the subject line
Your name, complete old postal or email address and the new address that you would like to change it to. You will receive an email confirmation that your request has been received and processed.
You can also contact us by mail at: Fitness Warehouse, 148 Port Road, Hindmarsh, SA 5007.
Your Online Account
When setting up an online account on our website, you will be prompted to select a password. The retrieval of personal information relating to you and your order history is only available to you if you provide the correct password that you have created. After providing your password, you can edit or delete your information at any time through the “my account” page. If you forget your password, you can request that it be emailed to your email address. We will not give passwords out over the phone, nor will we email them to a different address than the one used to register. If you request to have your password emailed to you, your credit card information will be automatically deleted from your profile for your protection.
Marketing email communications
At various points on our website you have the option to join our email list and receive information about our products, services and offers. Also, if you provide us with your email address when you register online or update your account, log-in, place an order, opt-in to receive our emails, shop online, request a catalogue or participate in a contest, promotion or survey, you may automatically be added to our email list and receive marketing or promotional information from us. If you do not wish to receive Fitness Warehouse marketing emails, you may opt out by clicking on the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of all our marketing emails.
Links To Other Sites
To enhance your shopping experience, our website may include links to other sites outside our family of brands. Those websites will have their own privacy policies that you may wish to review. Fitness Warehouse has no responsibility for these linked websites, outside of our family of brands.
Cookies And Web Beacons
Cookies are bits of information that we automatically store on your computer if your computer accepts cookies. We use both session cookies, which are deleted after you close your browser, and persistent cookies, which remain on your computer until they expire or you delete them. Cookies do not retain any personally identifiable information such as your name, address or any financial information, on your computer. We use cookies to recognise you and your preferences in order to improve the shopping process and provide you with a customized experience on our website. Fitness Warehouse places a unique user ID number on your cookie which allows us to access information that we can then use to improve your shopping experience, such as holding items in your shopping bag, accessing your address book, or providing you with customized pages based on your past viewing or purchasing history. If you do not wish to have cookies on your system, you can set your browser preferences to refuse them. In order to disable cookies, please consult your browser’s “help” section for instructions. Web beacons are small strings of code that are placed in a web page. They are sometimes called “clear GIFs” (Graphics Interchange Format) or “pixel tags”. Web beacons are most often used in conjunction with cookies to monitor activity on our websites. When you visit a particular web page, web beacons notify us of your visit. Since web beacons are used in combination with cookies, if you disable cookies the web beacons will only detect an anonymous website visit.
Security
The security of your information is very important to us. We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and Secure Payment Gateways to protect the security of your online order information. SSL technology encrypts your order information to protect it from being decoded by anyone other than Fitness Warehouse. Once you enter the checkout page your computer will begin communicating with our server in secure mode. When a customer is making a purchase from the website, the secure payment gateway eWAY communicates with the banking network to confirm the validity of the credit card used and the availability of funds. You can tell that you are in secure mode by the following:• The “http” in the web address will be replaced by “https”• Depending on the browser, you will see either a padlock or a solid key in the lower section of the browser window Only browsers that use the 256-bit Secure Socket Layer technology are able to order through our websites. If your browser does not support SSL, you can get an upgrade at Microsoft’s or Mozilla’s home page. While we implement these and other security measures on our sites, please note that 100% security is not always possible. You play a role in protecting your information as well. Because your password permits access to your personal information, please keep your password secret and do not disclose it to others.
Privacy of Young Children
Fitness Warehouse is concerned about the privacy of young children and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from a child under 13. We do not intend to sell products to children on our websites and all children’s products we sell are intended for purchase by adults only.
Accessing Our Web Sites From Outside Australia
All online orders will be accepted and fully processed in and shipped from Australia and all information you provide will be securely maintained on our web servers. By providing your information to us, you agree that all personal information will be used in accordance with this privacy policy. We do not ship outside of Australia.
Privacy Policy Updates
We may update our privacy policy from time to time and our use of the information we collect is subject to the terms of the privacy policy in effect when we collect that information. Whenever we make a change, we will post a notice on our newsletter and we encourage you to check our policy periodically. If we propose to modify our policy in a way that would significantly change the way that we use your information, we will provide you with a meaningful way to opt out of those new uses. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please contact us: Fitness Warehouse, 148 Port Road, Hindmarsh, SA 5007 or on email inquiries@fitnesswarehouse.com.au
Thank you for your subscription
Quantity
Add to Cart
Powered By Discount Ninja
×
[[BODY]]
[[TIMER_FOOTER]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON1_LABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON2_LABEL]]
×
[[HEADER]]
[[MINIMIZED]]
[[BODY]]
[[FOOTER]]
[[TIMER_FOOTER]]
Powered By Discount Ninja
[[TEXT]]
×
Powered By Discount Ninja
[[HEADER]]
[[BODY]]
[[FOOTER]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON1LABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON2LABEL]]
[[NOTHANKSBUTTONLABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON1LABEL]]
[[ACTIONBUTTON2LABEL]]
[[NOTHANKSBUTTONLABEL]]
[[TEXT]]
[[HEADER]]
Powered By Discount Ninja
[[BODY]]
[[QUANTITY_LABEL]]
[[PRICE_LABEL]]
[[TIER_ROW]]
[[PRICE]]
[[LABEL]]
[[HEADER]]
[[BODY]]
[[FOOTER]]
[[ROW]]
